{"questions": [{"question": "what is the nickname od the sydney is harbour bridge? ", "answer": "Affectionately named the Coathanger by locals, it's an intrinsic part of the city; you can walk or cycle across it and even climb to its peak for incredible views. The iconic bridge took eight years to build and opened in 1932. It's made of 53,000 tonnes of steel and six million hand-driven rivets."}, {"question": "what is the nickname of sydney? ", "answer": "The 2021 census recorded the population of Greater Sydney as 5,231,150. meaning the city is home to approximately 66% of the state's population. Nicknames of the city include the 'Emerald City' and the 'Harbour City'."}, {"question": "are funnel web spiders dangerous? ", "answer": "All funnel-web spider bites should be treated as potentially life-threatening, even though only approximately 10% to 15% of bites are venomous. Since the venom from the funnel-web spider bite is highly toxic, all species should be considered potentially dangerous."}, {"question": "where did ac/dc start its career? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "where did richard clapton start its career? ", "answer": "Richard Clapton as one of Australia's foremost singer/songwriters, paved the way for subsequent generations of songwriters to write about the experience of being Australian. When Richard began his recording career in 1974, Australia was still in the grip of the cultural cringe."}, {"question": "how strong is sydney is harbour bridge? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "who has the guinness world record for the largest swimsuit group? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what is the oldes street in Australia? ", "answer": "George Street in Sydney is the oldest street in Australia. It started out as a track from the site of Captain Arthur Phillip's settlement at what is now The Rocks, leading southward into the area of today's Central train station."}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the sydney opera house? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the grand organ? ", "answer": "Notre-Dame's famous Grand Organ is the largest organ in France, consisting of approximately 8,000 pipes, a console with five keyboards and pedals, and 109 stops. Its largest pipes stand an impressive 32 feet tall."}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the australian museum? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the mint building? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the university of sydney? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "who attended the national institute of dramatic art? ", "answer": "Considered one of the top acting schools in the world, the National Institute of Dramatic Art's most famous graduates include Cate Blanchett, Mel Gibson, Baz Luhrmann, Grant Bowler, Colin Friels, Jessica Marais, Catherine Martin, Robyn Nevin and Sam Worthington."}, {"question": "what can you tell me about the great barrier reef? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "are spiders eaten in australia? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "where can I find a Kangaroo? ", "answer": "Kangaroos are large marsupials that are found only in Australia."}, {"question": "how many kangaroos are there in Australia? ", "answer": "Kangaroos are indigenous to Australia and New Guinea. The Australian government estimates that 42.8 million kangaroos lived within the commercial harvest areas of Australia in 2019, down from 53.2 million in 2013."}, {"question": "what is a kangaroo? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what is a box jellyfish? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "are there snakes in australia? ", "answer": "Australia has around 140 species of land snake, and 32 recorded species of sea snakes. Some 100 Australian snakes are venomous, although only 12 are likely to inflict a wound that could kill you."}, {"question": "do tasmanian devil really exist? ", "answer": "The Tasmanian devil is the world's largest carnivorous marsupial, reaching 30 inches in length and weighing up to 26 pounds, although its size will vary widely depending on where it lives and the availability of food."}, {"question": "do australians like beer? ", "answer": "As you probably already know, beer in Australia is a pretty big deal. It is one of the most popular alcoholic drinks across the country. If you have a mind to join the locals in downing a few amber ales while you are here, the tips in this guide will help you figure out how to order and most importantly what to drink."}, {"question": "do australians like wine? ", "answer": "There is a $3.5 billion domestic market for Australian wines, with Australians consuming approximately 500 million litres annually. Norfolk Islanders are the second biggest per capita wine consumers in the world with 54 litres."}, {"question": "are there pink lakes? ", "answer": " Lake Hillier is located on the coast of Western Australia's Middle Island. This relatively small lake has a distinctly pink hue year-round, and its water still appears pink when removed. Other pink hypersaline lakes tend to change color depending on the season and temperature."}, {"question": "what is the hero is name in the legend of zelda? ", "answer": "Link is a brave, skilled warrior and the hero of The Legend of Zelda series. Over the course of the series, he has appeared in a variety of ages and forms, ranging from child to young adult, and in Twilight Princess, also appears in the form of a wolf."}, {"question": "what are the names of the ghosts who chae pac man and ms. pac-man? ", "answer": "5. Each of the four ghosts in the game has both Japanese and English names. In Japan they started as Fickle, Chaser, Ambusher and Stupid. Their English names are Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Clyde."}, {"question": "what is the name of the mythbusters' crash test mummy? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what is an oxford comma? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "who was the captain of the enterprise in the pilot episode of star trek? ", "answer": "Kirk as captain of the starship USS Enterprise. Captain Pike, as played by Jeffrey Hunter in the original pilot \"The Cage\". Pike first appeared as the main character of the original unaired pilot episode for Star Trek: The Original Series, \"The Cage\", portrayed by Jeffrey Hunter."}, {"question": "what is the symbol for the modulus operator in C? ", "answer": "The modulo operator, denoted by %, is an arithmetic operator. The modulo division operator produces the remainder of an integer division."}, {"question": "what function is automatically called at the beginning of a C++ program? ", "answer": "The first function is _start(), which is typically provided by the C runtime library, linked in automatically when your program is compiled."}, {"question": "which computer programming languages whas introduced by IBM in 1957? ", "answer": "1957 \u2013 FORTRAN (first compiler) 1957 \u2013 COMTRAN (precursor to COBOL) 1958 \u2013 LISP."}, {"question": "what does the acronym SMTP represent? ", "answer": "<span jscontroller=\"BicQqd\" jsname=\"XtloMb\">Simple <span jsaction=\"click:sKUsF\" role=\"tooltip\" tabindex=\"0\"><g-bubble jscontroller=\"QVaUhf\" data-ci=\"\" data-du=\"200\" data-tp=\"5\" jsaction=\"R9S7w:VqIRre;\" jsshadow=\"\"><span jsname=\"d6wfac\" class=\"povykd\" data-enable-toggle-animation=\"true\" data-extra-container-classes=\"ZLo7Eb\" data-hover-hide-delay=\"1000\" data-hover-open-delay=\"500\" data-send-open-event=\"true\" data-theme=\"0\" data-width=\"250\" role=\"button\" style=\"display:inline-block\" tabindex=\"0\" jsaction=\"vQLyHf\" jsslot=\"\" data-ved=\"2ahUKEwip2JyonuD5AhVSG7kGHfoRC0YQmpgGegQIEBAD\"><span jsname=\"ukx3I\" class=\"JPfdse\" data-bubble-link=\"\" data-segment-text=\"Mail Transfer\">Mail Transfer"}, {"question": "what does the acronym MPEG represent? ", "answer": "MPEG is a standard file format for compressing video images so that they can be stored or sent by email more easily. MPEG is an abbreviation for ' Motion Picture Experts Group'. [computing]"}, {"question": "what does the acronym GIMP represent? ", "answer": "GIMP is an acronym for GNU Image Manipulation Program. It is a freely distributed program for such tasks as photo retouching, image composition and image authoring. It has many capabilities."}, {"question": "what does the acronym GNU represent? ", "answer": "<span jscontroller=\"BicQqd\" jsname=\"XtloMb\">The GNU operating system is a complete free software system, upward-compatible with Unix. GNU stands for \u201cGNU's Not Unix.\u201d It is pronounced as one syllable with a hard g. <span jsaction=\"click:sKUsF\" role=\"tooltip\" tabindex=\"0\"><g-bubble jscontroller=\"QVaUhf\" data-ci=\"\" data-du=\"200\" data-tp=\"5\" jsaction=\"R9S7w:VqIRre;\" jsshadow=\"\"><span jsname=\"d6wfac\" class=\"povykd\" data-enable-toggle-animation=\"true\" data-extra-container-classes=\"ZLo7Eb\" data-hover-hide-delay=\"1000\" data-hover-open-delay=\"500\" data-send-open-event=\"true\" data-theme=\"0\" data-width=\"250\" role=\"button\" style=\"display:inline-block\" tabindex=\"0\" jsaction=\"vQLyHf\" jsslot=\"\" data-ved=\"2ahUKEwjrzdzjn-D5AhWCLLkGHZ5hCf8QmpgGegQIGBAD\"><span jsname=\"ukx3I\" class=\"JPfdse\" data-bubble-link=\"\" data-segment-text=\"Richard Stallman\">Richard Stallman"}, {"question": "who is considered as the first programmer? ", "answer": "Who was the first computer programmer? In the 1840s, Ada Lovelace became the first computer programmer, inspite of the fact that the Analytical Engine (the computer that she designed the programs for) wasn't ever manufactured."}, {"question": "has a robot ever killed a person? ", "answer": "Robert Nicholas Williams (May 2, 1953 \u2013 January 25, 1979) was an American factory worker who was the first known human to be killed by a robot. While working at the Ford Motor Company Flat Rock Casting Plant, Williams was killed by an industrial robot arm on January 25, 1979."}, {"question": "who was hitchbot? ", "answer": "hitchBOT was a Canadian hitchhiking robot created by professors David Harris Smith of McMaster University and Frauke Zeller of Ryerson University in 2013."}, {"question": "are self-driving cars safe? ", "answer": "Many experts say that self-driving cars can be trained to be safer than human drivers. With the sensors and cameras monitoring and guiding, these cars can not only sense their environment but also can anticipate what's coming up ahead, which humans are not capable of."}, {"question": "who invented the compiler? ", "answer": "Grace Murray Hopper was one of the first computer programmers to work on the Harvard Mark I. She was also a United States Navy rear admiral, helped develop COBOL -- one of the first high-level programming languages -- and invented the first compiler, a program that translates programming code to machine language."}, {"question": "who created the python programming language? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "is mark zuckerberg a robot? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what did the robot call it is creator? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "why did you run away? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what kind of salad do robots like? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what did you eat for lunch? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "why did robots get angry so often? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "why should not r2d2 be allowed in movies? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "what is your favorite style of music? ", "answer": ""}, {"question": "", "answer": ""}, {"question": "", "answer": ""}]}